Hello and welcome. I'm Chris Warman,
the admissions director here at Complete Care at Green Acres,
a five star rated skilled nursing facility for quality measures.
We are centrally located here in Toms River, New Jersey.
Upon entering our facility,
you'll be greeted by our warm and friendly receptionist and welcomed into our
beautifully renovated lobby.
We are host of 162 short-term rehab and long-term care beds.
Our rehab unit has an impressive 33 private suites,
along with semi-private options as well.
Each room comes with its own full restroom,
TV and mini fridge to make our residents stay as comfortable as possible.
While with us,
we have a beautiful dining room where our residents can come to eat, relax,
and enjoy entertaining recreational activities.
Our dietary department caters to our residents specific needs and diets.
Hi,
my name is Christine Kaminski and I'm the Director of nursing here at Complete
Care Green Acres Complete Care.
Green Acres boasts an experienced nursing staff equipped to manage even the most
complex cases.
The interdisciplinary care team prides itself on getting to know each patient
personally and developing an individualized plan of care.
Each patient is part of our Complete Care family.
This is our rehabilitation gym. Our therapy modules include physical,
occupational, and speech therapy, and our gym is open seven days a week.
We are very proud of the success our rehab team has consistently shown.
Each therapist has a unique approach to maximize your time spent during your
rehab journey. Here at Green Acres,
Our newly renovated rehab unit boast a cozy lounge where families and residents
can relax and enjoy each other's company.
Nestled in the center of our rehab unit is a beautifully outdoor courtyard where
our residents and families can enjoy a nice walk, smell some flowers,
or just go out for some fresh air.
Thank you for joining me on this virtual tour of complete care at Green Acres.
We look forward to the opportunity of assisting you or your loved ones on their
rehabilitative journey.